Contact

ameiners@fuse.net

www.linkedin.com/in/amy-meiners-64b48064 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Nursing

Teaching

Public Speaking

Certifications

ACLS and BLS Instructor

NAPPI (Non-Abusive Psychological and Physical Intervention) Certified Trainer

Certified Emergency Nurse

BLS, ACLS, PALS, NRP certifications

TNCC

Amy Meiners

BSN, RN, CEN; Stroke Coordinator

Cincinnati, Ohio Area

Summary

Experienced Stroke Coordinator of a Primary Stroke Center and two Acute Stroke Ready Hospitals, with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Emergency Nursing, professional development in healthcare, Customer Service, Microsoft Word, and Advanced Cardiac Life Support (ACLS). Strong professional graduated from Bethesda School of Nursing/CTC and the University of Cincinnati.

Experience

Mercy Health (formerly Catholic Health Partners) 24 years

East Market Stroke Coordinator January 2017 - Present (3 years 7 months) Cincinnati Area, KY

Emergency Department RN August 1996 - February 2017 (20 years 7 months) Cincinnati Area, KY

RN, BSN, CEN, Emergency Department Educator May 2009 - January 2017 (7 years 9 months)

Disaster Coordinator Interim October 2012 - July 2013 (10 months) mercy health anderson hospital

ASPR Grant, Coordination of Disaster Drills with local fire and Greater Cincinnati Health Council, Maintain inventory of hospital assets

Nursing Clinical Administrator
October 2002 - June 2006 (3 years 9 months)

Education

Bethesda School of Nursing/CTC ASN

University of Cincinnati BSN